Narrator: fathom is an assistant
with vision, for blind and low-vision people.
It used to have five modes.
You had to pick one
before you could ask anything.
Now it’s one conversation.
You just ask.
[Mellow guitar music]
[Listening chime]
You: What’s in front of me?
[Heard chime]
fathom: A stainless steel kettle
and your pour-over coffee setup
are about 6 feet away,
at your 11 o’clock.
Be careful, just in case
there’s hot water in the kettle.
[Listening chime]
You: What does this say?
[Heard chime]
fathom: It’s October’s electric bill.
It’s $84.77, due by the 12th.
Would you like me
to read all the details?
[Listening chime]
You: Where did I leave my keys?
[Heard chime]
fathom: You told me they’re
on the hook by the door.
I remember what you tell me.
[Listening chime]
You: Take me to the kitchen.
[Heard chime]
fathom: Keep heading forward
for about 12 feet,
and then the door to the kitchen
will be at 9 o’clock.
You’ll notice a change in the floor texture,
because it’s tile.
Narrator: fathom is live on the App Store,
free to download.
Find it at fathomvision.app.
Made to be heard.